It looks like snow!
Amazing!
So it looks like this year's energy is fading away.
Tomorrow we don't have school, so can we see the flowers?
That sounds fun! I'll prepare some food!
Me too!
Hey, hey.
Good idea!
All right!
Oh, sorry, I decided everything by myself...
Don't worry. It's no problem for me.
I'll bring something.
Thank you.
Kouki is always causing trouble.
Don't worry about it.
Kouki, Rin-chan!
Tomorrow, let's meet up at the park!
Okay!
All right...
So, 9 o' clock!
The flowers won't open until noon.
So, 10 o'clock!
I might miss GranSazers...
Let's meet at noon.
Daikichi!
Where are the sweets?
Aren't they below the sink?
Oh yeah!
It might rain tomorrow.
They said it'll be a spring storm.
Storm?
It's already raining!
It's really raining.
Can we make some charms against the rain?
Daikichi!
The rain stopped!
You did it.
The teru teru bouzu saved us!
They fell off because of the storm...
What a green smell!
The flowers disappeared!
Hey!
Kouki-kun!
Daikichi!
They're in full bloom in the sky!